alliedshirts.com 2017-06-06

# Custom T-Shirts - Allied Shirts Privacy Policy

**Effective Date: October 8, 2012**

Allied Shirts is committed to protecting your privacy while providing quality services that give you an enjoyable and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Allied Shirts website and governs data collection and usage. By using the Allied Shirts website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. The Allied Shirts website is the website contained at http://www.AlliedShirts.com and all pages and subpages therein.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

Allied Shirts collects personally identifiable information when you register or order, such as your e-mail address, physical address, name, and phone number, and credit card information. Allied Shirts also collects information not personally identifiable, such as zip code, city and state.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Allied Shirts. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses, templates made, path through the site, and operating system information. This information is used by Allied Shirts for the operation of its services, to maintain quality of service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Allied Shirts web site.

Allied Shirts encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Allied Shirts so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Allied Shirts is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Allied Shirts web site.

**Use of your Personal Information:**

Allied Shirts collects and uses your personal information to operate the Allied Shirts web site and deliver the services you have requested. Allied Shirts also uses your personally identifiable information from time to time to inform you of other products or services available from Allied Shirts and its affiliates. Allied Shirts may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. Note that at any time you may opt out of being contacted by Allied Shirts for any research or product updates, through clear links at the bottom of every email.

Allied Shirts does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Allied Shirts may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Allied Shirts may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Allied Shirts, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Allied Shirts does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Allied Shirts keeps track of the web sites and pages our customers visit within and from the Allied Shirts web site, in order to determine what Allied Shirts services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Allied Shirts to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Allied Shirts will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Allied Shirts or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Allied Shirts; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Allied Shirts, or the public.

**Use of Cookies**

The Allied Shirts web site may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you register with the Allied Shirts site or services, a cookie helps Allied Shirts to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Allied Shirts web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Allied Shirts features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Allied Shirts services or Web sites you visit.

**Security of your Personal Information**

Allied Shirts secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Allied Shirts secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Allied Shirts will not record, store, or save your Credit Card Number without your express consent and notice from Allied Shirts.

**Changes to this Statement**

Allied Shirts will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Allied Shirts encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Allied Shirts is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**

Allied Shirts welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Allied Shirts has not adhered to this Statement, please use the inquiry form to contact us. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
